Guide to the Office of the University Treasurer records, 1893-ongoing UA.10.01.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Office of the University Treasurer records
1893-ongoing
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Duke University. Office of the University Treasurer
UA.10.01.0001
191.9 Linear Feet
The Treasurer is an officer of the University whose duties have included supervision of contracts, relations with the Duke Endowment, and management of the Bursar's Office, student loans, and investments. The position of Treasurer is established by the By-laws of the University. In 1995, the Treasurer's post was taken up by the chief financial and administrative officer, the Executive Vice President. The bulk of the collection consists of correspondence to and from individuals who served the University as Treasurer and the subject files they created while in office, including grants and contracts but also ledger and account books. The collection ranges in date from 1893-ongoing.
Provenance
The Office of the University Treasurer records were received by the University Archives as transfers over a period of time. Accession UA2014.0084 (Boxes 86-132) transferred November 2014.
Biographical/Historical note
The position of Treasurer is established by the By-laws of the University. The Treasurer is an officer of the University whose duties have included supervision of contracts, relations with the Duke Endowment, and management of the Bursar's Office, student loans, and investments. Ex officio, the Treasurer has served on the board of Highland Hospital and has been active in disbursing monies provided by the Duke Endowment. In 1995, the Treasurer's post was taken up by the chief financial and administrative officer, the Executive Vice President.
Scope and Contents note
The bulk of the collection consists of correspondence to and from individuals who served the University as Treasurer and the subject files they created while in office, including grants and contracts. There are a handful of photographs of Highland Hospital in Asheville, N.C. in addition to legal papers such as wills and deeds of gift. Oversize materials include many account and ledger books for the early-mid part of the 20th century. One of the many benefits of this collection is official paperwork that pertains to many artifacts/collections the University has obtained as gifts from individuals such as Doris Duke and the Trent family. The collection ranges in date from 1893-ongoing.
Related Material
Robert Lee Flowers Records, 1891-1968, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Biographical Reference Collection, 1972-2004, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Board of Trustees Records, 1860-ongoing, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Board of Trustees Reference Collection, 1941-2002, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Business Division records, 1938-1948, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Trinity College, Randolph County, N.C. collection, 1836-1990, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Vice President for Business and Finance records, 1962-1985, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Access Restrictions
For a period of twenty-five years from the origin of the material, permission in writing from the office of origin and the University Archivist is required for use. After twenty-five years, records that have been processed may be consulted with the permission of the University Archivist.
Conditions Governing Access
Records, such as search committee files or others pertaining to employment where individuals are identified, are closed for 70 years.
Duke Homestead (Durham, N.C.); Ledgers (account books); Biddle, Mary Duke, 1887-1960; Trinity College (Durham, N.C.) -- Finance; Duke University -- Alumni and alumnae; Duke University -- Administration; Duke University -- Endowments; Duke University -- Buildings; Duke Endowment; Duke Construction Company; Duke University. Business and Finance Division; Duke University. Dining Halls; Duke University. Divinity School; Duke University. Hospital; Duke University -- Finance; Duke University -- Funds and scholarships; Duke University -- Students; Duke University. Board of Trustees; Duke, James Buchanan, 1856-1925; Highland Hospital, Asheville, N.C.; Kittrell College, Kittrell, N.C.; Duke University. Library; Duke University. Marine Laboratory; Duke University. Medical Center. Library. Historical Collection; Duke University. Office of Alumni Affairs
- Treasurer's Office, 1909-1979
  Scope and Contents note
  Includes correspondence, subject files, and contracts/agreements/grants. Boxes 1-5 contain accession A75-105. Box 5 also includes one folder from A78-4. Box 6 includes accessions A91-36, A92-62, A93-22, A75-40. Box 41 contains accession UA2006-0029.
  - Correspondence, 1930-1948 by correspondent (Box 1)
    - A (Box 1)
    - B (Box 1)
    - C (Box 1)
    - D (Box 1)
    - E (Box 1)
    - F (Box 1)
    - G (Box 1)
    - H (Box 1)
    - I (Box 1)
    - J (Box 1)
    - K (Box 1)
    - L (Box 1)
    - M (Box 1)
    - N (Box 1)
    - O (Box 1)
    - P (Box 1)
    - S (Box 1)
    - Sands, Alex H. Jr., 3 accordion folders (Box 1)
    - Smith, Willis (Box 1)
    - T (Box 1)
    - W (Box 1)
  - Accounting Procedures, Financial Overview, 1925 (Box 1)
  - Subject Files, 1924-1953
    - Dr. Albert Anderson Proposition (Box 1)
    - Applications (Box 1)
    - Auditor's Report (Box 1)
    - B. N. Duke Endowment Fund (Box 1)
    - Braxton Craven Portrait Fund (Box 1)
    - J. B. Duke Building Fund (Box 1)
    - Building Fund Reports (Box 1)
    - Burroughs Adding Machines (Box 1)
    - Thomas Holley Chivers Collections (Box 1)
    - Comite Des Voyages D'Etudes En France, Inc. (Box 1)
    - Departmental Reports (Box 1)
    - Dormitory Operations (Box 1)
    - Deeds (Box 1)
  - Subject Files, 1924-1953 cont'd (Box 2)
    - J. B. Duke Building Fund -- Account Old Campus (Box 2)
    - Duke Construction Company (Box 2)
    - Duke Endowment Appropriation for Hospital Changes (Box 2)
    - Duke Endowment Building Fund 1 (Box 2)
    - Duke Endowment Building Fund 2 (Box 2)
    - Duke Endowment Building Fund 3 (Box 2)
    - Duke University Athletic Council Stadium Fund (Box 2)
    - Contract with Horace Trumbauer (Box 2)
    - Duke Endowment Hospital Equipment Appropriation (Box 2)
    - Duke Homestead (Box 2)
    - Duke University Research Fellow (Box 2)
    - City of Durham Water Department (Box 2)
    - Easley Cotton Mills (Box 2)
    - Eastern Association of Colleges and Universities Business Officers (Box 2)
    - Endowment Income -- Duke Power Company (Box 2)
    - Endowment (Box 2)
    - Endowment Investments (Box 2)
  - Subject Files, 1924-1953 cont'd (Box 3)
    - General Education Board -- Division of Cooperation in Education and Race Relations (Box 3)
    - Executive Committee Minutes (Box 3)
    - Faculty Club (Box 3)
    - Faculty Houses (Box 3)
    - Freight Claims (Box 3)
    - The Fidelity Bank (Box 3)
    - First National Trust Company (Box 3)
    - Fuses (Box 3)
    - Furniture (Box 3)
    - General Education Board (Box 3)
    - George A. Fuller Company (Box 3)
    - Flowers Collection (Box 3)
    - Guaranty Trust Custody Account (Box 3)
    - Guaranty Trust Company of New York -- Investments (Box 3)
    - Gymnasium Building Fund (Box 3)
    - Gymnasium and Faculty Houses Account (Box 3)
    - Hospital -- Duke University (Box 3)
    - Insurance (Box 3)
    - Inventories (Box 3)
    - Lambeth Scholarship (Box 3)
    - Law Lectures (Box 3)
    - Law School Administrative Committee Minutes of Meetings (Box 3)
    - Lawnmowers -- S. P. Townsend and Co. (Box 3)
    - Liability Insurance (Box 3)
    - Library (Box 3)
    - Library Books -- Special Appropriations -- Duke Endowment (Box 3)
    - Duke University Library (Box 3)
    - Duke University -- Library Budget (Box 3)
    - Library Budget 1928-1929 (Box 3)
    - Library Budget 1929-1930 (Box 3)
  - Subject Files, 1924-1953 cont'd (Box 4)
    - Loan Funds (Box 4)
    - Markham, C. B. Personal (Box 4)
    - Miscellaneous Papers (Box 4)
    - Conference Reports (Box 4)
    - Mordecai Portrait Fund (Box 4)
    - National Research Council (Box 4)
    - Process (Box 4)
    - Publication Board (Box 4)
    - Registry of Stills (Box 4)
    - Repairs (Box 4)
    - Research Grants (Box 4)
    - Reports (Box 4)
  - Subject Files, 1924-1953 cont'd (Box 5)
    - Scholarships (Box 5)
    - Southern Association of College and University Business Offices (Box 5)
    - Hospital (Box 5)
    - Summer School (Box 5)
    - Contracts, 1941-1947 (Box 5)
    - Contract for Training of German Experts (Box 5)
    - Watson Microwave (Box 5)
    - Watson Laboratories (Box 5)
    - Chemical Warfare Service Antibiotics Research (Box 5)
    - E. S. M. W. T. (Box 5)
    - Influenza Commission (Box 5)
    - N. D. R. C. - Project B (Box 5)
    - A. S. T. P. -- Medical (Box 5)
    - N. D. R. C. (Box 5)
    - Navy Department Bureau of Ships (Box 5)
    - U. S. Navy (Box 5)
    - O. S. R. D. (Box 5)
    - O. S. R. D. -- Project B (Box 5)
    - O. S. R. D. -- Research of Dr. Callaway (Box 5)
    - N. S. T. P. -- Medical (Box 5)
    - Agar Research (Box 5)
    - Army -- Finance School (Box 5)
    - Chemistry Defense Research (Box 5)
    - Engineering Science Management War Training, ESMWT (Box 5)
    - Interamerican Workshop (Box 5)
    - NRL Helium Research (Box 5)
    - U. S. Epidemiological Survey (Box 5)
    - Naval V12 Program (Box 5)
    - Navy College Training Unit (Box 5)
    - N. S. T. P. -- Medical, V-12 Program (Box 5)
    - Army-Air Force (Box 5)
    - O. R. I. (Box 5)
    - Training Service (Box 5)
    - Dr. Perlzweig's Research (Box 5)
    - O. S. R. D. Research - Dr. Gross (Box 5)
    - O. S. R. D. Research -- Dr. Hobbs (Box 5)
    - Dr. Charles Hauser (Box 5)
    - N. D. R. C. Project A (Box 5)
    - N. D. R. C. Physical War Research (Box 5)
    - V. A. Study of Neural Regeneration (Box 5)
    - O. N. R. Atomic Fission (Box 5)
    - Audit Report of Duke University -- Medical (Box 5)
  - Contracts, Agreements and Grants, 1927-1986 (Box 6)
    - Agreement -- Fielding L. Marshall -- Art Museum (Box 6)
    - Extension of City Limits (Box 6)
    - Fanjoy, P.S. - Chapel organ tuning and maintenance, 1932 (Box 6)
    - Kittrell College (Box 6)
    - R. L. Flowers and F. M. Hanes (Box 6)
    - Flowers House Release (Box 6)
    - Duke Construction Instruments turned over to Forestry Dept. (Box 6)
    - Building Costs -- Duke Construction Company (Box 6)
    - Chemistry Defense Research (Box 6)
    - Agreement -- New Furniture (Box 6)
    - Contract with A. C. Lee to Supervise New Buildings (Box 6)
    - Prefabricated House Contracts (Box 6)
    - Building Permits (Box 6)
    - Duke University and A. C. Lee -- Contract, Duke Univ. and Office of Horace Trumbauer, N. C. (Box 6)
    - Medical Care Commission (Box 6)
    - D. U. A. A. Southern Conference (Box 6)
    - Contract -- William Muirhead Construction -- Golf Course (Box 6)
    - Duke University and William D. Murray Agreement [head football coach] (Box 6)
    - Agreement -- Duke University -- Horace Trumbauer Hospital Addition (Box 6)
    - Annexation Petition (Box 6)
    - S. W. Myatt Papers (Box 6)
    - Contract with W. M. Ervin Bill of Sale (Box 6)
    - Campaign Fund -- Arts and Science (Box 6)
    - Environmental Concerns Committee (Box 6)
    - Duke University Stores Operation Computer System Audit (Box 6)
    - Ford Foundation Grant (Box 6)
    - S. C. Harward Speeches (Box 6)
    - S. C. Harward Speeches to Pathologists (Box 6)
    - Intangible Taxes-Unitrusts (Box 6)
    - Internal Revenue Service (Box 6)
    - Investment Management Service Fees (Box 6)
    - Sam and Barbara Jones (Box 6)
    - Sandy Creek (Box 6)
    - Terry Sanford Property (Box 6)
    - Student Loans (Box 6)
    - Tax File (Box 6)
    - Taxes, Non-resident aliens (Box 6)
    - Tuition Prepayment Fund (Box 6)
    - Report of Investment Booklets (Box 6)
    - Renewal Copyright Blue and White Dear Oh Duke (Box 6)
    - Radium Contact and Renewal (Box 6)
    - J. B. Duke -- Gold Watch (Box 6)
    - Permits -- Removal of Duke Bodies (Box 6)
    - Index to Documentary Pictures of Washington Duke Homestead (Box 6)
    - U. S. A. Re: Nurses Homes Agreements (Box 6)
    - Receipts for Articles turned over to J. P. Breedlove (Box 6)
    - Contract -- Duke University and W. O. Frank and office of Horace Trumbauer, Graduate Dormitory (Box 6)
    - Bill of Sale from Mrs. Marmaduke H. Floyd (Box 6)
    - Contract -- E. Henry Cappelmann Purchase and Sale, Duke University Library (Box 6)
    - Release executed by William O. Frank and W. E. Frank, Horace Trumbauer (Box 6)
    - W. Bryan Bolich Deed of Gift [Duke Family Table] (Box 6)
  - UA2006-0029 (Box 41)
    - Athletics Fund, 1924 (Box 41)
    - Class of 1909 Gift (Box 41)
    - Class of 1911 Gift (Box 41)
    - Class of 1912 Gift (Box 41)
    - Class of 1913 Gift (Box 41)
    - Class of 1914 Gift (Box 41)
    - City of Durham Construction Permits, 1939 (Box 41)
    - Laurinburg Normal and Industrial Institute, 1953 (Box 41)
    - Trinity College Financial Statement, 1924 (Box 41)
    - Trinity Park High School Treasurer Report, 1919-1920 (Box 41)
    - Casket Warranty, William P. Few (Box 41)
    - Two sample class rings (Box 41)
- Duke Endowment, 1915-1957, Rural Churches, 1927-1969, James B. Duke Superannuate Fund, 1915-1955, Trustees' Records, 1924-1954
  Boxes 7-13 include accessions A91-36, A92-62, A93-22, A75-40.
  - Duke Endowment Reports, 1926-1937 (Box 7)
  - Duke Endowment Reports, 1938-1945 (Box 8)
  - Duke Endowment Reports, 1946-1951 (Box 9)
  - Payments, 1939-1951 (Box 9)
  - 1927-1969 (Box 10)
    - Rural Church Department (Box 10)
    - Duke Endowment for Operating Rural Churches (Box 10)
    - Correspondence -- Duke Endowment for Operating Rural Churches (Box 10)
    - Correspondence with Reference to New Form of Certificate (Box 10)
    - Correspondence -- Appropriations for Operating Rural Churches (Box 10)
    - Miscellaneous File (Box 10)
    - J. B. Duke Church Extension Fund -- Appropriations for Summer Work (Box 10)
    - Appropriations for Building Rural Churches, Architect's Fees (Box 10)
    - Duke Endowment for Operating Rural Churches -- List (Box 10)
    - Appropriations for Operating Rural Churches -- List -- Monthly Check (Box 10)
  - 1927-1969 (Box 11)
    - Appropriations for Operating Rural Churches -- List -- Monthly Checks (Box 11)
    - Reports of Committee on Rural Churches (Box 11)
    - Tabor Church, Stedman Circuit, Fayetteville District, Cumberland County Township (Box 11)
    - Tabor Church, Littleton Circuit, Rocky Mount District (Box 11)
    - Union Church, Mamers Charge, Raleigh District (Box 11)
    - Union Church, Pasquotank Circuit, Elizabeth City District (Box 11)
    - Uwharrie Church, Troy Circuit, Fayetteville District (Box 11)
    - Wallace Church, Wallace-Rose Hill Circuit (Box 11)
    - Walnut Grove Church, Cedar Grove Circuit, Durham District (Box 11)
    - Walstonburg Church, Farmville Circuit, Rocky Mount District (Box 11)
    - Warren's Grove Church, Person County, Person Circuit, Durham District (Box 11)
    - Warren Plains Church, Warrenton Circuit, Rocky Mount District (Box 11)
    - Warsaw Church, Faison-Warsaw Charge, Wilmington District (Box 11)
    - Wesley's Chapel, Newton Grove Circuit, Raleigh District (Box 11)
    - Wendell Church, Zebulon Circuit, Raleigh District (Box 11)
    - Wesley Memorial Church, Epworth-Wesley Circuit, Wilmington District (Box 11)
    - Wesley Memorial Church, Columbia District, Elizabeth City District (Box 11)
    - White Oak Church, Bladen Circuit, Wilmington District (Box 11)
    - Winsor Church, Bladen Circuit, Wilmington District (Box 11)
    - Winterville Church, Ayden Circuit, New Bern District (Box 11)
    - Winton Church, Murfreesboro-Winton Circuit, Weldon District (Box 11)
    - Woodington Church, Pink Hill Charge, New Bern District (Box 11)
    - Woodland Church, Pink Hill Circuit, New Bern District (Box 11)
    - Woodland Church, Rich Square Circuit, Weldon District (Box 11)
    - Woodsdale Church, Person Circuit, Durham District (Box 11)
    - Youngsville Church, Franklinton Circuit, Raleigh District (Box 11)
    - Zion Church, Town Creek Circuit, Wilmington District (Box 11)
    - Zion Church, Gates Circuit, Elizabeth City District (Box 11)
    - Zion Church, Richmond Circuit, Rockingham District (Box 11)
    - Zion Church, Norlina Circuit, Rocky Mount District (Box 11)
    - Wesley Chapel, Wesley Chapel Charge, Barringer Township, Iredell County, Statesville District (Box 11)
    - Wesley Chapel Church, Davie County, Farmington Circuit (Box 11)
    - Wesley's Chapel Church, Jackson County, Waynesville District, Sylva Charge, Sylva Township (Box 11)
    - Wesley Chapel, Shepherds Charge, Statesville District (Box 11)
    - Wesley Chapel, Pfeiffer Charge, Salisbury District (Box 11)
    - Wesley Chapel Church, Guilford County, Greensboro District, Oak View Charge, High Point Township (Box 11)
    - Wesley's Chapel, South Fork Charge, Gastonia District (Box 11)
    - West Bend Church, Asheboro Circuit, Greensboro District (Box 11)
    - West Chapel Church, Asheboro Circuit, High Point District (Box 11)
    - West Cramerton Church, McAdenville Charge, Gastonia District (Box 11)
    - West Jefferson, West Jefferson Charge, Ashe County, Statesville District, West Jefferson Township (Box 11)
    - West Jefferson Church, Jefferson Circuit, Mount Airy District (Box 11)
    - West Marion Church, Cross Mill Charge, Marion District (Box 11)
    - Whitakers Chapel, Shoals Charge, Surry County, Winston-Salem District, Pilot Mountain Township (Box 11)
    - Whitnel Church, Hudson Circuit, Statesville District (Box 11)
    - Whittier Methodist, Whittier Charge, Waynesville District (Box 11)
    - West Jefferson Church, Jefferson Circuit, Mount Airy District (Box 11)
    - West Marion Church, Cross Mill Charge, Marion District (Box 11)
    - Whitakers Chapel, Shoals Charge, Surry County, Winston-Salem District, Pilot Mountain Township (Box 11)
    - Whitnel Church, Hudson Circuit, Statesville District (Box 11)
    - Whittier Methodist, Whittier Charge, Waynesville District (Box 11)
  - 1927-1969 (Box 12)
    - Wightman Church, Polkton Charge, Charlotte District (Box 12)
    - Wilkesboro Methodist Church, Wilkesboro Charge, Statesville District (Box 12)
    - Williamston's Chapel, South Iredell Circuit, Statesville District (Box 12)
    - Wingate Church, Union County, Monroe Township, Wingate Charge, Charlotte District (Box 12)
    - Wolf Mountain Church, Glenville Circuit, Waynesville District (Box 12)
    - Woodfin Church, Asheville Charge, Asheville District (Box 12)
    - Woodleaf Church, Woodleaf Charge, Salisbury District (Box 12)
    - Yadkinville Church, Yadkinville Charge, Winston-Salem District (Box 12)
    - Yakin College Church, Shiloh Charge, Thomasville District (Box 12)
    - Zion, Richfield Charge, Rowan County, Morgan Township, Salisbury District (Box 12)
    - Zion, Unionville Charge, Union County, Goose Creek Township, Charlotte District (Box 12)
    - Zion Methodist Church, Franklin Heights Charge, Winston-Salem District (Box 12)
    - Zion Church, Unionville-New Hope Charge, Charlotte District (Box 12)
    - Zion Church, Morganton Circuit, Marion District (Box 12)
    - Zion Church, Burke County, Drexel Charge, Morganton Township, Marion District (Box 12)
    - J. B. Duke Church Extension Fund Brooksdale Church, Brooksdale Circuit, Durham District (Box 12)
    - J. B. Duke Church Extension Fund Arapahoe Church, Oriental Circuit (Box 12)
    - J. B. Duke Church Extension Fund Stanhope Church, Spring Hope Circuit, Washington District (Box 12)
    - J. B. Duke Church Extension Fund Union Church, Murfreesboro Circuit, Weldon District (Box 12)
    - J. B. Duke Church Extension Fund Union Church, Albemarle Circuit, Salisbury District (Box 12)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 12)
    - Union Church, Forsyth County, Lewisville Circuit (Box 12)
    - Union Church, Wilkesboro Circuit, Statesville District (Box 12)
    - Union Chapel Church, Davie County, Mocksville Circuit, Thomasville District (Box 12)
    - Union Chapel Church, Stanly County, Albemarle Circuit, Salisbury District (Box 12)
    - Union-Grove, Union Grove Charge, Iredell County, Statesville District, Union Grove Township (Box 12)
    - Unity, Oak Grove-Unity Charge, Rowan County, Salisbury District, Atwell Township (Box 12)
    - Vanderburg Church, Shepherds Charge, Statesville District (Box 12)
    - Vickrey, Guilford Circuit, Guilford County, Jamestown Township, Greensboro District (Box 12)
    - Vickrey Church, Guilford County, Guilford Circuit, Greensboro District (Box 12)
    - Wade Church, Lilesville Charge, Charlotte District, Anson County, Wadesboro Township (Box 12)
    - Warrensville Church, Warrensville Charge, Statesville District, Ashe County, Clifton Township (Box 12)
    - Warrensville Church, Warrensville Circuit, Mount Airy District (Box 12)
    - Waxhaw Church (Box 12)
    - Waxhaw Circuit, Charlotte District (Box 12)
    - Weaverville, Weaverville Charge, Buncombe County, Asheville District, Reems Creek Township (Box 12)
    - Webb's Chapel Church, Lincoln County, Rock Springs Charge, Gastonia District, Catawba Springs Township (Box 12)
    - Weddington Church, Weddington Charge, Charlotte District, Union County, Sandy Ridge Township (Box 12)
    - Wentworth Church, Reidsville Charge, Greensboro District, Rockingham County, Wentworth Township (Box 12)
    - Olive Branch Church, Fuquay Circuit, Raleigh District (Box 12)
    - Ormond's Chapel, Hookerton Circuit, New Bern District (Box 12)
    - Oriental Church, Oriental Circuit, New Bern District (Box 12)
    - Page Memorial Church, Biscoe Circuit, Rockingham District (Box 12)
    - Palmer's Grove Church, Hillsboro Circuit, Durham District (Box 12)
    - Pamlico Church, Oriental Circuit, New Bern District (Box 12)
    - Pantago Church, Pantago-Belhaven Circuit, Elizabeth City District (Box 12)
    - Pembroke Church, Lumberton Circuit, Wilmington District (Box 12)
    - Pine Forest Church, Goldsboro Circuit, New Bern District (Box 12)
    - Pink Hill Church, Pink Hill Circuit, New Bern District (Box 12)
    - Poplar Springs Church, Jonesboro Circuit, Fayetteville District (Box 12)
    - Princeton Church, Princeton Circuit, Raleigh District (Box 12)
    - Roe Church, Atlantic Charge, New Bern District (Box 12)
    - Rones Chapel, Mount Olive Circuit, New Bern District (Box 12)
    - Rose Hill Church, Wallace-Rose Hill Circuit, Wilmington District (Box 12)
    - Roseland Church, Aberdeen-Vass Charge, Fayetteville District (Box 12)
    - Rougemont Church, Rougemont Circuit, Durham District (Box 12)
    - Rowland Church, Rowland Circuit, Fayetteville District (Box 12)
    - Sandy Cross Church, Sandy Cross Charge, Rocky Mount District (Box 12)
    - Saxapahaw Church, Saxapahaw Charge, Durham District (Box 12)
    - Scotts Hill Church, Scotts Hill Circuit, Wilmington District (Box 12)
    - Seaboard Church, Seaboard Circuit, Weldon District (Box 12)
    - Smiths Church, Lumberton Circuit, Rockingham District (Box 12)
    - Sneads Ferry Church, Scotts Hill Circuit, Wilmington District (Box 12)
    - Snow Hill Church, Snow Hill Circuit, New Bern District (Box 12)
    - Stantonsburg Church, Stantonsburg Charge, Washington District (Box 12)
    - Star Church, Biscoe Circuit, Montgomery County Township, Rockingham District (Box 12)
    - Stokes Church, Robersonville Circuit, Rocky Mount District (Box 12)